tvnew.in 2008-03-31

# Names Beyond a leading ICANN accredited registrar. domain names, web hosting , web development , domain transfer, domain renewal, email services

| 

NamesBeyond.com Privacy Policy 

Effective as of September 1, 2003  
Last updated February 10, 2006  
  
---  
Why A Privacy Policy?   
Names Beyond respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) represents our commitment to protecting your privacy. By visiting any of the sites offered by NamesBeyond.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. For questions on the Privacy Policy, please contact Names Beyond at [info@namesbeyond.com](mailto:info@namesbeyond.com).  
Introduction to Policy:  
In this Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy"), the terms "you", "your" and "Registrant" refer to each and every user of internet services provided by NamesBeyond.Com. The terms "we", "us" and "our" refer to NamesBeyond.Com who provides domain name and other services (the "Services"). Website refers to www.NamesBeyond.Com. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the " [Service Agreement](http://www.namesbeyond.com/pages/additionaldocs/agreements.html) ".  
Information Collected:  
Pursuant to the [Service Agreement](http://www.namesbeyond.com/pages/additionaldocs/agreements.html), you will provide to us and we will require from you information about each domain name registered with NamesBeyond.Com, including the names, addresses, telephone numbers and e-mail addresses of individuals designated as points of contact for a given domain name (collectively the "Information").  
Use of Information:  
We will use the information to operate, maintain and manage the Services. We will use your information to bill you properly, administer your account, administer your domain name registration, and properly perform the Services. We will, only with your consent, use the information collected to monitor and improve its internal programs and operations. We will use the information collected to notify you about upcoming developments or news and/or important notices or promotions affecting your registration or the Services by way of a newsletter. We may copy, distribute, display, transmit, prepare derivative works from or otherwise use the information only in accordance with this Policy and with any rules, requirements, policies, guidelines or regulations which are or may in the future be adopted, developed or imposed by any related Registry Authorities or by law. We will not sell your information to any third party without your permission. We will take reasonable precautions regarding any sensitive financial information (i.e., credit card numbers, banking information) or security information. Please note, however, that, consistent with the current policies for the domain name system, certain information about you must remain available in the publicly accessible registration database.   
Does NamesBeyond.com Share the Information It Receives?  
Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, you will receive notice whenever personal information (excluding WHOIS Information) about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share that information. We share personal information as described below:   
• WHOIS Information: ICANN, the regulator for all gTLD domain names, requires NamesBeyond.com to make certain information collected in connection with the registration, renewal or transfer of a domain name, available to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" text-based WHOIS service. This public information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the nameserver information associated with your domain name, but does not include demographic, financial or Internet usage information. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy we refer to this information collectively as your "WHOIS Information." We do not control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information.  
• Database and Zone Files: Database and Zone Files: We must make certain information about you available to the general public registry database look-up and directory services. When you register or reserve a domain name through us, we will disclose your domain name and its associated Internet Protocol ("IP") numbers (the "zone files") to the applicable domain name registry in order to make your chosen domain name a functional address on the Internet.   
• Advertisers: We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
• Partners: We sometimes partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policy of such third parties before submitting any personal information to a partner.  
• Agents: We engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to NamesBeyond.com for any secondary purposes.  
• Service Providers: We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. In addition, certain of our enhanced services such as our Search Engine Optimization services require that we contact Search engines, Internet directories and various search engines on your behalf. Many of our service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  
• Business Transfer: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if NamesBeyond.com or all or substantially all of its assets were ever to be acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.  
• Compliance: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Services Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of NamesBeyond, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may share certain information about you with those who are responsible for handling your account or performing other necessary services that you require. Although we may share sensitive financial information (i.e., credit card numbers, banking information) or security information with such parties where necessary and appropriate, we will not share such information with other third parties, except as required by law, in connection with litigation or arbitration proceedings directly relating to a domain name registration or Services we provide. Please note, however, that, consistent with the current policies for the domain name system, certain information about you must remain available in the publicly accessible registration database.  
Your Consent:  
By applying for or using the Services or by applying for and registering a domain name you acknowledge that you have read and agree to be bound by all terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to us, you evidence your consent to us storing and using the personal information submitted as indicated in this Privacy Policy.  
Modifications to Policy:  
You agree that we, in our sole discretion, may modify the Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any of the changes to our Privacy Policy, you will have the opportunity of contacting us, and controlling your personal information to the extent allowed for the proper management, control maintenance and operation of the relevant domain name system. We may, if appropriate, take steps to restrict or expand the accessibility and amount of personally identifying information publicly available in the registration database. In any event, your sole remedy will be as outlined in the Service Agreement.  
External Links:  
Some pages or sites within the Website contain links to other websites. We do not accept any responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those web sites, please visit them directly.  
Use of Cookies:  
We may use cookie files to make it easier for users to access our Website and Services. A cookie is stored on your hard-drive and can contain information although the only personal information a cookie may contain is information that you yourself provide. A cookie cannot read data from your hard-drive. Besides using the information as described above, NamesBeyond utilizes cookies to control the flow of the ordering processes by maintaining the state of your online transactions. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.   
  
Is Information About Me Secure?  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
We protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents.  
We always encrypt your credit card number before storing it in our database, and protect the database from normal access to any user or general employee. 

We do not share your password or other personally identifying information with any parties other than yourself or someone expressly authorized by you.  
  
How Can I Access My Information?  
NamesBeyond provides each user with their customized Control Panel, with a unique Username and Password combination, for the limited purpose of viewing, and in certain cases updating their information. When users update information, NamesBeyond may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.  
Services For Children:  
NamesBeyond does not sell services for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.  
Use of Your E-Mail Address:  
From time to time, NamesBeyond.com may use your personal information to contact you by electronic mail concerning our services. These communications are intended to inform you of important information regarding your account, or about general services provided by NamesBeyond.com. If you do not want to receive email from us regarding new services, please click the "unsubscribe" link which is included at the bottom of any email you receive from NamesBeyond.com. However, in order to fulfill our service obligations to you, we will continue to send you emails regarding your account administration, as well as any necessary information, such as renewal instructions.   
What Happens to my Information if I Cancel My NamesBeyond account?  
If your NamesBeyond account is canceled, NamesBeyond will continue to store your information, but not in an accessible manner using a control panel or similar mechanisms. As a result, cancellation of your account does not mean that your personal information is deleted from our databases. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information as necessary in order to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, or provide marketing and other updates to you as a prior customer of the company’s services.  
Contacting the Web Site:  
If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at our Canadian headquarters at   
4141 Yonge Street, Suite 204,  
Toronto, ON M2P 2A8  
Canada  
In the United States:  
NamesBeyond.com,   
922 South Woodbourne Road, #122   
Levittown, PA - 19057-1001  
United States  
(c) 2000-2006 NamesBeyond.com
